Guide to the Western Film Collection
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- July 2006 Acquisition, 1916-1982; 2.33; (19 boxes)
  - Day of the Badman, 1958 (Box 24 (Oversize))
  - Day of the Locust, 1974 (Box 24 (Oversize))
  - Day of the Outlaw, 1959 (Box 24 (Oversize))
  - The Deadly Companions, 1962 (Box 24 (Oversize))
  - Decision at Sundown, 1957 (Box 24 (Oversize))
  - A Debtor to the Law, 1919 (Box 24 (Oversize))
  - Desert Fury, 1958 (Box 24 (Oversize))
  - Desperadoes of Dodge City, 1948 (Box 24 (Oversize))
  - Did You Hear the One About the Traveling Saleslady?, 1968 (Box 25 (Oversize))
  - Dirty Dingus Magee, 1970 (Box 25 (Oversize))
  - Domino Kid, 1957 (Box 25 (Oversize))
  - Dragoon Wells Massacre, 1957 (Box 25 (Oversize))
  - The Driftin' Kid, 1941 (Box 25 (Oversize))
  - Drums Across the River, 1954 (Box 25 (Oversize))
  - The Duchess and the Dirtwater Fox, 1976 (Box 25 (Oversize))
  - Duel at Diablo, 1966 (Box 25 (Oversize))
  - Dynamite Canyon, 1941 (Box 25 (Oversize))
  - The Eagle and the Hawk, 1950 (Box 25 (Oversize))
  - East of Eden, 1954 (Box 25 (Oversize))
  - Escape from Fort Bravo / Rode, Vaquero, 1960 (Box 25 (Oversize))
  - An Eye for an Eye, 1966 (Box 25 (Oversize))
  - The Fighting Lawman, 1953 (Box 25 (Oversize))
  - Fighting Man of the Plains, 1949 (Box 25 (Oversize))
  - The First Texan, 1956 (Box 25 (Oversize))
  - Flaming Frontier, 1958 (Box 25 (Oversize))
  - Flaming Star, 1960 (Box 25 (Oversize))
  - Flesh and the Spur, 1957 (Box 25 (Oversize))
  - For a Few Dollars More, 1967 (Box 26 (Oversize))
  - Fort Courageous, 1965 (Box 26 (Oversize))
  - Fort Massacre, 1958 (Box 26 (Oversize))
  - Fort Utah, 1966 (Box 26 (Oversize))
  - Forty Guns, 1957 (Box 26 (Oversize))
  - Four Fast Guns, 1959 (Box 26 (Oversize))
  - The Frisco Kid, 1979 (Box 26 (Oversize))
  - From Hell to Texas, 1958 (Box 26 (Oversize))
  - From Noon Till Three, 1976 (Box 26 (Oversize))
  - Frontier Woman, 1956 (Box 26 (Oversize))
  - The Furies, 1950 (Box 26 (Oversize))
  - Fury at Showdown, 1957 (Box 26 (Oversize))
  - Fury at Gunsight Pass, 1956 (Box 26 (Oversize))
  - The Getaway, 1972 (Box 26 (Oversize))
  - Ghost Patrol, 1936 (Box 26 (Oversize))
  - Ghost Town, 1956 (Box 26 (Oversize))
  - Ghost Town Renegades, 1947 (Box 26 (Oversize))
  - Goin' South, 1978 (Box 26 (Oversize))
  - Gold Fever, 1952 (Box 26 (Oversize))
  - The Grapes of Wrath, 1940 (Box 26 (Oversize))
  - Gray Eagle, 1977 (Box 27 (Oversize))
  - Great Adventures of Wild Bill Hickok, circa 1950 (Box 27 (Oversize))
  - The Great Scout and Cathouse Thursday, 1976 (Box 27 (Oversize))
  - The Great Sioux Massacre, 1965 (Box 27 (Oversize))
  - The Great Smokey Roadblock, 1976 (Box 27 (Oversize))
  - Green Grass of Wyoming, 1948 (Box 27 (Oversize))
  - Gun Battle at Monterey, 1957 (Box 27 (Oversize))
  - Gun Duel in Durango, 1957 (Box 27 (Oversize))
  - Gun Glory, 1957 (Box 27 (Oversize))
  - A Gunfight, 1970 (Box 27 (Oversize))
  - Gunfight at Comanche Creek, 1963 (Box 27 (Oversize))
  - Gunmen of the Rio Grande, 1965 (Box 27 (Oversize))
  - Guns for San Sebastian, 1968 (Box 27 (Oversize))
  - Gunsight Ridge, 1957 (Box 27 (Oversize))
  - Gunsmoke, 1947 (Box 27 (Oversize))
  - Half Way to Hell, 1961 (Box 27 (Oversize))
  - Hang Em High, 1971 (Box 27 (Oversize))
  - The Hangman, 1959 (Box 27 (Oversize))
  - Hangman's Knot, 1952 (Box 27 (Oversize))
  - The Hard Man, 1957 (Box 27 (Oversize))
  - Harry and Tonto, 1974 (Box 28 (Oversize))
  - Hearts of the West, 1975 (Box 28 (Oversize))
  - Heaven's Gate, 1981 (Box 28 (Oversize))
  - Hell's Outpost, circa 1958 (Box 28 (Oversize))
  - The Hellbenders, 1967 (Box 28 (Oversize))
  - High Hell, 1958 (Box 28 (Oversize))
  - High Lonesome, 1950 (Box 28 (Oversize))
  - High Noon, 1965 (Box 28 (Oversize))
  - The Hired Gun, 1957 (Box 28 (Oversize))
  - The Hired Hand, 1971 (Box 28 (Oversize))
  - Hombre, 1967 (Box 28 (Oversize))
  - Honeymoon Ranch, 1920 (Box 28 (Oversize))
  - Honky Tonky, 1940, 1955 (Box 28 (Oversize))
  - Hopalong Cassidy, 1948 (Box 28 (Oversize))
  - In Old Amarillo, 1951 (Box 28 (Oversize))
  - Indian Agent, 1948 (Box 28 (Oversize))
  - The Ivory Handled Gun, circa 1950 (Box 28 (Oversize))
  - Jesse James Rides Again, circa 1955 (Box 28 (Oversize))
  - Joe Dakota, 1957 (Box 28 (Oversize))
  - Junior Bonner, 1972 (Box 28 (Oversize))
  - Kansas Pacific, 1953 (Box 28 (Oversize))
  - The King and Four Queens, 1956 (Box 28 (Oversize))
  - Kit Carson, 1947 (Box 28 (Oversize))
  - Klondike Fury, 1942 (Box 28 (Oversize))
  - Land Raiders, 1969 (Box 28 (Oversize))
  - The Last Gunfighter, 1961 (Box 29 (Oversize))
  - The Last Round-Up, 1934 (Box 29 (Oversize))
  - Law of the Lash, 1947 (Box 29 (Oversize))
  - Little Big Man / A Man Called Horse, 1970, 1973 (Box 29 (Oversize))
  - The Littlest Horse Thieves, 1976 (Box 29 (Oversize))
  - The Living Desert / The Vanishing Prairie, 1953, 1971 (Box 29 (Oversize))
  - The Lone Ranger / The Lost City of Gold, 1956, 1958 (Box 29 (Oversize))
  - Lonely Are the Brave, 1962 (Box 29 (Oversize))
  - The Long Riders, 1980 (Box 29 (Oversize))
  - Loser's End, 1935 (Box 29 (Oversize))
  - Lucky Lady, 1975 (Box 29 (Oversize))
  - The Man from Laramie, 1955 (Box 29 (Oversize))
  - The Man from Texas, 1948 (Box 29 (Oversize))
  - Man in the Saddle, 1951 (Box 29 (Oversize))
  - Man in the Shadow, 1957 (Box 29 (Oversize))
  - Man in the Wilderness, 1971 (Box 29 (Oversize))
  - Man of the West, 1958 (Box 29 (Oversize))
  - Man with the Steel Whip, 1954 (Box 29 (Oversize))
  - The Marauders, 1955 (Box 29 (Oversize))
  - Massacre Canyon, 1954 (Box 29 (Oversize))
  - McClintock, 1964 (Box 30 (Oversize))
  - The Misfits, 1961 (Box 30 (Oversize))
  - The Missouri Breaks, 1976 (Box 30 (Oversize))
  - Money, Women And Guns, 1959 (Box 30 (Oversize))
  - Montana Territory, 1952 (Box 30 (Oversize))
  - The Mountain Men, 1980 (Box 30 (Oversize))
  - Mule Train, 1956 (Box 30 (Oversize))
  - Murder on the Yukon, 1940 (Box 30 (Oversize))
  - Mustang, 1959 (Box 30 (Oversize))
  - Mustang Country, 1976 (Box 30 (Oversize))
  - My Darling Clementine, 1946 (Box 30 (Oversize))
  - The Naked Dawn, 1955 (Box 30 (Oversize))
  - Naked Gun, 1957 (Box 30 (Oversize))
  - Naked Hills, 1956 (Box 30 (Oversize))
  - Navajo Run, 1964 (Box 30 (Oversize))
  - Nevada, 1951 (Box 30 (Oversize))
  - No Name on the Bullet, 1959 (Box 30 (Oversize))
  - North Dallas 40, 1979 (Box 30 (Oversize))
  - Oklahoma Crude, 1973 (Box 30 (Oversize))
  - Old Oklahoma Plains, 1952 (Box 31 (Oversize))
  - Old Overland Trail, 1952 (Box 31 (Oversize))
  - The Outlaw Josie Wales, 1976 (Box 31 (Oversize))
  - Outlaw Women, 1952 (Box 31 (Oversize))
  - Outlaw's Son, 1957 (Box 31 (Oversize))
  - The Outlaw Is Coming, 1964 (Box 31 (Oversize))
  - Overland Pacific, 1954 (Box 31 (Oversize))
  - Overland to Deadwood, circa 1950 (Box 31 (Oversize))
  - The Overlanders, 1946 (Box 31 (Oversize))
  - Pack Train, 1953 (Box 31 (Oversize))
  - Painted Hills, 1951 (Box 31 (Oversize))
  - The Palomino, 1950 (Box 31 (Oversize))
  - Pals of the Golden West, 1951 (Box 31 (Oversize))
  - The Parson and the Outlaw, 1957 (Box 31 (Oversize))
  - Passage West, 1951 (Box 31 (Oversize))
  - Pawnee, 1957 (Box 31 (Oversize))
  - Perils of the Wilderness, 1955 (Box 31 (Oversize))
  - Phantom Stallion, 1954 (Box 31 (Oversize))
  - The Phantom Stage, circa 1950 (Box 31 (Oversize))
  - The Phantom Stagecoach, 1957 (Box 31 (Oversize))
  - Pioneer Justice, 1947 (Box 31 (Oversize))
  - The Plunderers, 1960 (Box 31 (Oversize))
  - Plunderers of Painted Flats, 1959 (Box 32 (Oversize))
  - Posse, 1975 (Box 32 (Oversize))
  - The Proud Ones, 1956 (Box 32 (Oversize))
  - Psycho, 1960 (Box 32 (Oversize))
  - Quantrill's Raiders, 1953 (Box 32 (Oversize))
  - Rachel and the Stranger, 1953 (Box 32 (Oversize))
  - Rage at Dawn, 1955 (Box 32 (Oversize))
  - Raiders of Old California, 1957 (Box 32 (Oversize))
  - Rancho Deluxe, 1975 (Box 32 (Oversize))
  - Rancho Notorious, circa 1956 (Box 32 (Oversize))
  - Range Beyond the Blue, 1947 (Box 32 (Oversize))
  - Ranger of Cherokee Strip, 1949 (Box 32 (Oversize))
  - The Rawhide Years, 1955 (Box 32 (Oversize))
  - Red Mountain, 1952 (Box 32 (Oversize))
  - Red River, circa 1953 (Box 32 (Oversize))
  - Red River Shore, 1953 (Box 32 (Oversize))
  - Red Sun, 1972 (Box 32 (Oversize))
  - The Restless Breed, 1957 (Box 32 (Oversize))
  - The Return of a Man Called Horse, 1976 (Box 32 (Oversize))
  - The Return of Frank James, 1951 (Box 32 (Oversize))
  - Return of the Frontiersman, 1950 (Box 33 (Oversize))
  - Return of the Plainsman, 1953 (Box 33 (Oversize))
  - Revolt at Fort Laramie, 1956 (Box 33 (Oversize))
  - Ride a Violent Mile, 1957 (Box 33 (Oversize))
  - The Ride Back, 1957 (Box 33 (Oversize))
  - Ride Beyond Vengeance, 1966 (Box 33 (Oversize))
  - Ride Lonesome, 1958 (Box 33 (Oversize))
  - Rider on a Dead Horse, 1962 (Box 33 (Oversize))
  - Riders of the Santa Fe, circa 1950 (Box 33 (Oversize))
  - Rio Grande, 1949 (Box 33 (Oversize))
  - Rio Grande Raiders, 1946 (Box 33 (Oversize))
  - River of No Return, 1954 (Box 33 (Oversize))
  - The Roaring West, 1935 (Box 33 (Oversize))
  - Rooster Cogburn, 1975 (Box 33 (Oversize))
  - Rough Night in Jericho, 1967 (Box 33 (Oversize))
  - Run For Cover, 1955 (Box 33 (Oversize))
  - Saddle the Wind, 1957 (Box 33 (Oversize))
  - Salt Lake Raiders, 1950 (Box 33 (Oversize))
  - San Antone Ambush, 1950 (Box 33 (Oversize))
  - Savage Red, Outlaw White, 1975 (Box 33 (Oversize))
  - The Savage Wild, 1970 (Box 34 (Oversize))
  - The Scalphunters, 1968 (Box 34 (Oversize))
  - Scandalous John, 1971 (Box 34 (Oversize))
  - Secret of Treasure Mountain, 1956 (Box 34 (Oversize))
  - Señor Jim, 1936 (Box 34 (Oversize))
  - Sequoia, 1953 (Box 34 (Oversize))
  - Seven Guns to Mesa, 1958 (Box 34 (Oversize))
  - Shampoo, 1975 (Box 34 (Oversize))
  - She Wore a Yellow Ribbon, 1949 (Box 34 (Oversize))
  - Sheriff of Wichita, 1948 (Box 34 (Oversize))
  - Shoot-Out at Medicine Bend, 1957 (Box 34 (Oversize))
  - Showdown, 1963 (Box 34 (Oversize))
  - Showdown at Abilene, 1956 (Box 34 (Oversize))
  - Showdown at Boot Hill, 1958 (Box 34 (Oversize))
  - The Siege at Red River, 1954 (Box 34 (Oversize))
  - Sierra Baron, 1958 (Box 34 (Oversize))
  - The Silent Stranger, 1975 (Box 34 (Oversize))
  - The Silver Bullet, 1935 (Box 34 (Oversize))
  - Silver Devil, 1940 (Box 35 (Oversize))
  - The Silver Whip, 1953 (Box 35 (Oversize))
  - Sing, Cowboy, Sing, 1937 (Box 35 (Oversize))
  - Six-Gun Gold, circa 1950 (Box 35 (Oversize))
  - Six Gun Trail, 1938 (Box 35 (Oversize))
  - Sometimes a Great Notion, 1971 (Box 35 (Oversize))
  - The Sons of Katie Elder, 1968 (Box 35 (Oversize))
  - Sons of New Mexico, 1954 (Box 35 (Oversize))
  - South of Northern Lights, 1922 (Box 35 (Oversize))
  - South of St. Louis, 1949 (Box 35 (Oversize))
  - The Spoilers, 1955 (Box 35 (Oversize))
  - Stage to Mesa City, 1947 (Box 35 (Oversize))
  - Stagecoach, 1966 (Box 35 (Oversize))
  - Stalking Moon, 1968 (Box 35 (Oversize))
  - Stallion Canyon, 1949 (Box 35 (Oversize))
  - Stars over Texas, 1946 (Box 35 (Oversize))
  - The Storm Rider, 1957 (Box 35 (Oversize))
  - The Story of Will Rodgers, 1952 (Box 35 (Oversize))
  - The Stranger in Canyon Valley, 1921 (Box 35 (Oversize))
  - A Stranger in Town, 1966 (Box 35 (Oversize))
  - The Stranger Returns, 1966 (Box 35 (Oversize))
  - Sugarfoot, 1951 (Box 36 (Oversize))
  - The Sundowners, 1950 (Box 36 (Oversize))
  - Support Your Local Sheriff, 1969 (Box 36 (Oversize))
  - Take a Hard Ride, 1975 (Box 36 (Oversize))
  - Tall Man Riding, 1955 (Box 36 (Oversize))
  - The Tall Texan, 1953 (Box 36 (Oversize))
  - Tell Them Willie Boy Is Here, 1970 (Box 36 (Oversize))
  - Ten Wanted Men, 1955 (Box 36 (Oversize))
  - Tennessee's Partner, 1958 (Box 36 (Oversize))
  - Tension at Table Rock, 1956 (Box 36 (Oversize))
  - Terror in a Texas Town, 1958 (Box 36 (Oversize))
  - Tex Granger Midnight Rider of the Plains, 1959 (Box 36 (Oversize))
  - Tex Rides With the Boy Scouts, 1937 (Box 36 (Oversize))
  - Texas Bad Man, 1953 (Box 36 (Oversize))
  - Texas Lady, 1955 (Box 36 (Oversize))
  - That Texas Jamboree, 1955 (Box 36 (Oversize))
  - They Rode West, 1954 (Box 36 (Oversize))
  - They Shoot Horses, Don't They?, 1970 (Box 36 (Oversize))
  - Three Young Texans, 1954 (Box 36 (Oversize))
  - Thunder Over the Plains, 1953 (Box 36 (Oversize))
  - Thunder River Feud, 1942 (Box 37 (Oversize))
  - Thunder Over Arizona, 1956 (Box 37 (Oversize))
  - Tim Holt, circa 1950 (Box 37 (Oversize))
  - Topeka, 1953 (Box 37 (Oversize))
  - Trail of the Rustlers, 1949 (Box 37 (Oversize))
  - Trails End, 1935 (Box 37 (Oversize))
  - The Treasure of Pancho Villa, 1955 (Box 37 (Oversize))
  - Treasure of Ruby Hills, 1955 (Box 37 (Oversize))
  - Treasure of Silver Lake, 1965 (Box 37 (Oversize))
  - Tumbleweed Trail, 1946 (Box 37 (Oversize))
  - Two Guns and a Badge, 1954 (Box 37 (Oversize))
  - Two Guys From Texas, 1948 (Box 37 (Oversize))
  - Two Rode Together, 1961 (Box 37 (Oversize))
  - Ulzanas Raid, 1972 (Box 37 (Oversize))
  - The Undefeated, 1969 (Box 37 (Oversize))
  - The Union Pacific, 1958 (Box 37 (Oversize))
  - Up the MacGregors!, 1967 (Box 37 (Oversize))
  - Utah Blaine, 1956 (Box 37 (Oversize))
  - The Vanishing American, 1955 (Box 37 (Oversize))
  - Vertigo, 1958 (Box 37 (Oversize))
  - The Violent Men, 1958 (Box 37 (Oversize))
  - Wagon Trail, 1935 (Box 37 (Oversize))
  - Wagon Wheels, circa 1945 (Box 38 (Oversize))
  - Wagonmaster, 1950 (Box 38 (Oversize))
  - Wanderer of the Wasteland, 1935 (Box 38 (Oversize))
  - War Paint, 1953 (Box 38 (Oversize))
  - Warlock, 1959 (Box 38 (Oversize))
  - Waterhole #3, 1967 (Box 38 (Oversize))
  - West of the Pecos, 1945 (Box 38 (Oversize))
  - Western Terror, circa 1950 (Box 38 (Oversize))
  - The Westerner, circa 1948 (Box 38 (Oversize))
  - Westworld, 1973 (Box 38 (Oversize))
  - When the Redskins Rode, 1951 (Box 38 (Oversize))
  - The White Buffalo, 1977 (Box 38 (Oversize))
  - The Wild Country, 1970 (Box 38 (Oversize))
  - Wild Harvest, 1958 (Box 38 (Oversize))
  - Wild Heritage, 1958 (Box 38 (Oversize))
  - Wild Rovers, 1971 (Box 38 (Oversize))
  - Winchester '73, 1950 (Box 38 (Oversize))
  - Winterhawk, 1975 (Box 38 (Oversize))
  - The Wonderful Country, 1959 (Box 39 (Oversize))
  - Wrangler's Roost, 1941 (Box 39 (Oversize))
  - The Wyoming Bandit, 1949 (Box 39 (Oversize))
  - Yellow Sky, circa 1955 (Box 39 (Oversize))
  - Young Jesse James, 1960 (Box 39 (Oversize))
  - Zandy's Bride, 1974 (Box 39 (Oversize))
- June 2010 Acquisition, undated; 0.08; (1 box)
  Purchased from WalterFilm.com on the Winlock William Miller, Jr. Memorial Fund, 2010.
  Consists of one pressbook.
  - The Lone Ranger Rides Again, undated (Box 40 (Oversize))
- November 2010 Acquisition, 1932-1934; 0.08; (1 box)
  Consists of pressbooks.
  Purchased from WalterFilm.com on the Frederick W. and Carrie S. Beinecke Fund for Western Americana, 2010.
  - Dangerous Crossroads, 1933 (Box 41 (Oversize))
  - Forbidden, 1932 (Box 41 (Oversize))
  - Hell and High Water, 1933 (Box 41 (Oversize))
  - The Important Witness, 1933 (Box 41 (Oversize))
  - The Last Trail, 1933 (Box 41 (Oversize))
  - The Man Trailer, 1934 (Box 41 (Oversize))
  - The Red Rider, 1934 (Box 41 (Oversize))
  - The Thundering Herd, 1933 (Box 41 (Oversize))
  - Tillie and Gus, 1933 (Box 41 (Oversize))
- October 2011 Acquisition, 1958-2001; 3; (3 boxes)
  Consists of press kits.
  Purchased from WalterFilm.com on the Frederick W. and Carrie S. Beinecke Fund for Western Americana, 2011.
  - 1941, 1979 (Box 42)
  - After Dark My Sweet, 1990 (Box 42)
  - Badlands, 1973 (Box 42)
  - Back to the Future Part III, 1990 (Box 42)
  - Big Fix, 1978 (Box 42)
  - Black Marble, 1980 (Box 42)
  - Bonanza, 1992 (Box 42)
  - Border, 1982 (Box 42)
  - Born in East L.A., 1987 (Box 42)
  - Bound For Glory, 1976 (Box 42)
  - Bret Maverick, 1981 (Box 42)
  - Bugsy, 1991 (Box 42)
  - California Suite, 1978 (Box 42)
  - Cattle King, 1963 (Box 42)
  - Chinatown, 1974 (Box 42)
  - City Slickers II, 1994 (Box 42)
  - Corvette Summer, 1978 (Box 42)
  - Cowboy Way, 1994 (Box 42)
  - Cowboys, 1971 (Box 42)
  - Days of Heaven, 1978 (Box 42)
  - Destiny Turns on the Radio, 1995 (Box 42)
  - Devil in a Blue Dress, 1995 (Box 42)
  - Dirty Harry, 1971 (Box 42)
  - Dragnet, 1987 (Box 42)
  - Electric Horseman, 1979 (Box 42)
  - Evening Star, 1996 (Box 42)
  - Far and Away, 1992 (Box 42)
  - Fargo, 1996 (Box 42)
  - The Great Scout and Cathouse Thursday, 1976 (Box 42)
  - Happy Texas, 1999 (Box 42)
  - Hard Country, 1981 (Box 42)
  - Heartland, 1979 (Box 42)
  - Hearts of the West, 1975 (Box 42)
  - Heaven's Gate, 1980 (Box 43)
  - Horse Whisperer, 1998 (Box 43)
  - Hot Lead and Cold Feet, 1978 (Box 43)
  - Indictment: The McMartin Trial, 1995 (Box 43)
  - L.A. Confidential, 1997 (Box 43)
  - The Last Hard Men, 1976 (Box 43)
  - Lawman, 1958 (Box 43)
  - Leaving Las Vegas, 1995 (Box 43)
  - The Legend of Nigger Charlie, 1972 (Box 43)
  - Legends of the Fall, 1994 (Box 43)
  - Less Than Zero, 1987 (Box 43)
  - Lone Star, 1996 (Box 43)
  - The Long Riders, 1980 (Box 43)
  - Lost In America, 1986 (Box 43)
  - Magnolia, 1999 (Box 43)
  - Man in the Wilderness, 1971 (Box 43)
  - The Man Who Loved Cat Dancing, 1973 (Box 43)
  - The Man Who Wasn't There, 2001 (Box 43)
  - The Master Gun Fighter, 1975 (Box 43)
  - Maverick, 1994 (Box 43)
  - Melvin and Howard, 1980 (Box 43)
  - The Misadventures of Sheriff Lobo, 1979 (Box 43)
  - Natural Born Killers, 1994 (Box 43)
  - North Dallas Forty, 1979 (Box 43)
  - Of Mice and Men, 1992 (Box 43)
  - The Onion Field, 1979 (Box 43)
  - Outlaw Josie Wales, 1976 (Box 43)
  - Pale Rider, 1985 (Box 44)
  - Patty Hearst, 1988 (Box 44)
  - Pat Garrett and Billy the Kid, 1973 (Box 44)
  - Places in the Heart, 1984 (Box 44)
  - Posse, 1993 (Box 44)
  - Postcards From the Edge, 1990 (Box 44)
  - The Postman Always Rings Twice, 1981 (Box 44)
  - Pulp Fiction, 1994 (Box 44)
  - Raggedy Man, 1981 (Box 44)
  - Raising Arizona, 1987 (Box 44)
  - Rio Lobo, 1971 (Box 44)
  - A River Runs Through It, 1992 (Box 44)
  - Shampoo, 1975 (Box 44)
  - Short Cuts, 1993 (Box 44)
  - Silence of the North, 1981 (Box 44)
  - Small Town Texas, 1976 (Box 44)
  - Sonny and Jed, 1974 (Box 44)
  - Tender Mercies, 1983 (Box 44)
  - Three Amigos, 1986 (Box 44)
  - Tickle Me, 1965 (Box 44)
  - The Trial of Billy Jack, 1974 (Box 44)
  - True Crime, 1999 (Box 44)
  - Two For Texas, 1997 (Box 44)
  - Two Jakes, 1996 (Box 44)
  - Who Framed Roger Rabbit?, 1988 (Box 44)
  - Wild Rovers, 1971 (Box 44)
  - Wyatt Earp, 1994 (Box 44)
  - Young Guns, 1998 (Box 44)
  - Zandy's Bride, 1974 (Box 44)
  - Zorro the Gay Blade, 1981 (Box 44)
- January 2012 Acquisition, 1970-2005; 0.38; (2 boxes)
  Consists of photographs, posters, lobby-cards, press and other ephemera relating to African American filmmakers of southern California.
  Purchased from Walter Reuben, Inc. on the Arthur Corbitt Hoskins Memorial Fund, 2012.
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically by name of filmmaker.
  - Bakeer, Donald
    - South Central - Press kit with five photographs, circa 1992 (Box 45)
  - Burnett, Charles
    - The Glass Shield - two 8" x 10" photographs, circa 1995 (Box 45)
  - Franklin, Carl
    - Devil in a Blue Dress - eight 8" x 10" color stills, circa 1995 (Box 45)
    - Devil in a Blue Dress - twelve 8.5" x 11.5" German lobby cards, circa 1995 (Box 45)
    - One False Move - Press kit with six photographs, circa 1992 (Box 45)
  - Hughes Brothers
    - American Pimp - one 8" x 10" photograph, circa 1999 (Box 45)
    - Dead Presidents - Press kit with four photographs, circa 1995 (Box 45)
    - Menace II Society - nine 8" x 10" photographs, circa 1993 (Box 45)
  - Rock, Chris
    - CB4 - Press kit with nine photographs, circa 1992 (Box 45)
  - Singleton, John
    - Boyz n the Hood - eight 9.5" x 13" Spanish lobby cards, circa 1991 (Box 45)
    - Boyz n the Hood - eight 11" x 14" US lobby cards, circa 1991 (Box 45)
    - Boyz n the Hood - twelve 8.5" x 12" German lobby cards, circa 1991 (Box 45)
    - Boyz n the Hood - Press kit with eighteen photographs, circa 1991 (Box 45)
    - Four Brothers - Press kit, circa 2005; 1; (1 CD-ROM) (Box 45)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Copies of electronic files may be requested through Access Services. Disk #: 2012.wa.13.0001
    - Poetic Justice - six 9.5" x 13" Spanish lobby cards, circa 1993 (Box 45)
    - Shaft - Press kit with eleven photographs, circa 2000 (Box 45)
  - Van Peebles, Melvin
    - Sweet Sweetback's Baadasssss Song - Pressbook, circa 1971; 2 (Box 46 (Oversize))
    - Sweet Sweetback's Baadasssss Song - 19" x 14" Review Poster containing two different reviews., circa 1971 (Box 46 (Oversize))
    - Watermelon Man - eight 11" x 14" lobby cards, circa 1970 (Box 46 (Oversize))
    - Watermelon Man - Pressbook with insert, circa 1970 (Box 46 (Oversize))
- June 2012 Acquisition, 1973-1978; 0.21; (1 box)
  Purchased from Royal Books, Inc. on the Arthur Corbitt Hoskins Memorial Fund, 2012.
  - Badlands, 1973 (Box 47)
  - Days of Heaven, 1978; 2 (Box 47)
- July 2012 Acquisition, 1936-1941; 0.21; (1 box)
  - Custer's Last Stand, 1936 (Box 48)
  - High Sierra, 1941 (Box 48)
- September 2012 Acquisition, 1949-1950; 0.08; (1 box)
  Purchased from Royal Books on the William Robertson Coe Fund No. 3, 2012.
  - Gun Crazy, 1950 (Box 49 (Oversize))
  - Thieves' Heaven, 1949 (Box 49 (Oversize))
- December 2012 Acquisition, 1911-2006; 4.84; (8 boxes)
  Consists of press kits, pressbooks, and promotional books and flyers.
  Box 50 (sound recording): Use of originals is restricted. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  Purchased from Walter Reuben, Inc. on the Frederick W. and Carrie S. Beinecke Fund for Western Americana, 2012.
  - 2 Days in the Valley - press kit, 1996 (Box 50)
  - 7 Faces of Dr. Lao - promotional book, 1964 (Box 50)
  - 8 Million Ways to Die - press kit, 1986 (Box 50)
  - Across the Great Divide - press kit, 1976 (Box 50)
  - The Adventures of Ford Fairlane - press kit, 1990 (Box 50)
  - The Alamo - promotional book, 1960 (Box 50)
  - Alamo Bay - press kit, 1985 (Box 50)
  - American Graffiti - press kit, 1978 (Box 50)
  - Anywhere But Here - press kit, 1999 (Box 50)
  - Apollo 13 - press kit, 1995 (Box 50)
  - Arizona - promotional book, 1940 (Box 50)
  - Around the World in 80 Days - promotional book, 1956 (Box 50)
  - Baby Boy - press kit, 2001 (Box 50)
  - Back to the Beach - press kit, 1987 (Box 50)
  - Back to the Future - press kit, 1985 (Box 50)
  - Back to the Future II - press kit, 1989 (Box 50)
  - Bakersfield P.D. - press kit, 1993 (Box 50)
  - Barbarosa - press kit, 1982 (Box 50)
  - Barfly - press kit, 1987 (Box 50)
  - Baywatch - press kit, 1992 (Box 50)
  - The Bear - press kit, 1989 (Box 50)
  - The Beverly Hillbillies - press kit, 1993 (Box 50)
  - Beverly Hills Cop II - press kit, 1987 (Box 50)
  - Beverly Hills Cop III - press kit, 1994 (Box 50)
  - The Big Green - press kit, 1995 (Box 50)
  - The Big Sleep - Warner pressbook, 1946
    Includes advertising supplement.
  - Biker Boyz - press kit, 2003 (Box 50)
  - Billy Jack - promotional book, 1971 (Box 50)
  - Bite the Bullet - promotional book, 1975 (Box 50)
  - Blade Runner - press kit, 1982 (Box 50)
  - Body Double - press kit, 1984 (Box 50)
  - Boogie Nights - press kit, 1997 (Box 50)
  - Breakheart Pass - press kit, 1976 (Box 50)
  - The Buddy Holly Story - promotional book, 1978 (Box 50)
    Includes one 7" "flexi disc" recording bound in book.
  - Buffalo Bill and the Indians, or Sitting Bull's History Lesson - promotional book, 1976 (Box 50)
  - Bugsy - pressbook, 1991
  - The Call of the Wild - press kit, 1997 (Box 50)
  - The Carpetbaggers - promotional book, 1964 (Box 51)
  - Casino - press kit, 1996 (Box 51)
  - Cheech and Chong's Nice Dreams - press kit, 1981 (Box 51)
  - Cimarron - press kit, 1960 (Box 51)